{
   
   
    "q1":{
            "question" : "1. What label catches all values except those specified?",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "otherwise",
                "option2" : "default",
                "option3" : "any",
                "option4" : "all"
                },
            "answer" : "2"
            },
       
    "q2":{
            "question" : "2.  Which event cannot be run globally?",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "onload",
                "option2" : "onkeypress",
                "option3" : "onclick",
                "option4" : "all can run globally"
                },
            "answer" : "4"
            }, 
    
    "q3":{
            "question" : "3. What value is returned by getMonth in April?",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "2",
                "option2" : "3",
                "option3" : "4",
                "option4" : "5"
                },
            "answer" : "2"
            },
    
    "q4":{
            "question" : "4. How do you define a numerical value?",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "var mynum = new Math;",
                "option2" : " var mynum = Math(6);",
                "option3" : "var mynum = 6;",
                "option4" : " Math.mynum = 6;"
                },
            "answer" : "3"
            },
    
    "q5":{
            "question" : "5. < noscript > tags will work",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "only with external Javascripts",
                "option2" : "with internal and external Javascripts",
                "option3" : "whether or not there is any Javascript",
                "option4" : "only in browsers that don't know what Javascript is"
                },
            "answer" : "3"
            },
    
    "q6":{
            "question" : "6. The same object can have how many properties and methods?",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "one or the other",
                "option2" : "one of each",
                "option3" : "as many as you want of one or the other",
                "option4" : "as many of both as you want"
                },
            "answer" : "4"
            },
     "q7":{
            "question" : "7. The code to obtain a random number between 5 and 9 inclusive is:",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "Math.floor((Math.random() * 5) + 4);",
                "option2" : "Math.floor((Math.random() * 4) + 4)",
                "option3" : "Math.floor((Math.random() * 4) + 5)",
                "option4" : "Math.floor((Math.random() * 5) + 5)"
                },
            "answer" : "4"
            },
       
    "q8":{
            "question" : "8. You define an array using",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "var new array = myarray;",
                "option2" : "var myarray = array new;",
                "option3" : "var new Array() = myarray;",
                "option4" : "var myarray = new Array();"
                },
            "answer" : "4"
            }, 
    
    "q9":{
            "question" : "9. What is the correct way to write a JavaScript array?",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "var colors = (1:'red', 2:'green', 3:'blue')",
                "option2" : "var colors = ['red', 'green', 'blue']",
                "option3" : "var colors = 'red', 'green', 'blue'",
                "option4" : "var colors = 1 = ('red'), 2 = ('green'), 3 = ('blue')"
                },
            "answer" : "2"
            },
    
    "q10":{
            "question" : "10. What is the correct JavaScript syntax to change the content of the HTML element below?                    < p id='demo' > This is a demonstration.</p>",
            "options"  :{
                "option1" : "document.getElementByName('p').innerHTML = 'Hello World!';",
                "option2" : "#demo.innerHTML = 'Hello World!';",
                "option3" : "document.getElementById('demo').innerHTML = 'Hello World!';",
                "option4" : "document.getElement('p').innerHTML = 'Hello World!';"
                },
            "answer" : "3"
            }
}
    
   
   
   
  